A Finding Aid to the Dorothy Weiss Gallery Records, circa 1964-2001 (bulk 1984-2000), in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Artist Files, circa 1964-2001; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 17.5 Linear feet Boxes 1-18, OV 21
  - Howard, Susan, General, circa 1995-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Hude, Katrina, Consignment Records, 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Huff, Jason, General, 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Hughto, Margie, General, 1980-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 20-21)
    Includes piece of handmade paper signed by Hughto.
  - Hunt, William, General, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 22)
    Includes slide transparency, possibly of Hunt; oversized material housed in OV 21.
  - Hunter, Justin, General, 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Hydman-Vallien, Ulrica, General, 1981-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Ikeda, Yoshiro, General, 1984, 1991-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Irwin, Jeff, Archival Resource Key (Box 6)
    - General, 1995-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1995-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Isupov, Sergei, General, 1996-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Iwata, Kiyomi, General, 1992-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 29)
    Includes samples of Auric Grid Hanging and Auric Grid Hanging Two; oversized material housed in OV 21.
  - Jacques, Frank, General, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Jameson, Philip, General, 1983-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Jeck, Doug, Archival Resource Key (Box 6)
    - General, 1990-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1995-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Jones, Cassandra, General, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Joseph, Bo, General, 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Joyce, Tim, General, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Kahl, Fred, General, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Kaneko, Jun, Archival Resource Key (Box 7)
    - Announcements and Press Releases, DW Gallery, 1988-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Biographies, Résumés, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Collector Records, 1990-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Consignment Records, 1990-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Contract, Bemis Center for Contemporary Art, 1992-1995, Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1986-2000, Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 6-8)
    - Inventory and Price Lists, circa 1986-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Invoices, 1990-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Loan Forms, 1989, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Printed Material, 1983-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Photographs of Kaneko, circa 1986-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1988-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 14-16)
  - Kaplan, Alissa, General, 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Karina, Elena, General, 1982-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Kehlmann, Robert, Archival Resource Key (Box 7)
    - General, 1978-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 19)
      Oversized material housed in OV 21.
    - Photographic Material, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Kendall, Gail, General, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Kerrigan, Thomas, General, circa 1983-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - King, David, General, circa 1988-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Kirillova, Julia, General, 1996-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Koblitz, Karen, Archival Resource Key (Box 7)
    - General, 1977-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Inventory Records, 1977-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Kohl, Joyce and Gayle Luchessa, General, 1978-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Kovatch, Ron, General, 1987-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Krasnican, Susie, General, circa 1988-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Krusoe, Sana, Archival Resource Key (Box 7)
    - General, 1980-1993, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1980-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Kuraoka, David, General, circa 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Kvapil, Jay, Announcement, DW Gallery, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - LaBianca, Lawrence, Archival Resource Key (Box 7)
    - General, 1994-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1994-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Laemmle, Cheryl, General, 1991-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Laky, Gyöngy, General, 1980-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Lancet, Marc, General, 1992-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Larocque, Jean-Pierre, General, 1995-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - La Scola, Judith, General, 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Lastomirsky, Geo, General, 1993-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Lawrence, Les, General, 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Leedy, Jim, General, 1987, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Levi, David and Dimitri Michaelides, 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Levin-Lau, Katherine, General, 1985-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Lieberman, Walter, General, 1994-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Lindquist, Mark, General, 1993, 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Lipofsky, Marvin, General, 1975-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Low-Beer, Susan, General, circa 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Lucero, Michael, Archival Resource Key (Box 8)
    - Announcements and Press Releases, DW Gallery, 1991-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Biographies, Résumés, 1990, 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Collector Records, 1991-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Consignment Records, 1991-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1991-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 17-18)
    - Loan Forms, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Price Lists, circa 1991-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Printed Material, 1983-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 21-23)
    - Re-sale Records, 1994-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 25-28)
  - Lynch, Nathan, General, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Mace, Flora and Joey Kirkpatrick, General, 1986-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Magel, Catherine, General, 1984-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Makins, James, Archival Resource Key (Box 8)
    - General, 1992-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1992-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Mangus, Kirk, General, 1983-1989, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Marak, Louis, Archival Resource Key (Box 8)
    - General, 1982-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 35-36)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1982-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 37-39)
  - Marioni, Paul, General, 1987, 1997-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Massaro, Karen, General, 1995-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Marquis, Richard, Archival Resource Key (Box 9)
    See also Bartneck, Lea.
    - Correspondence, 1979-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Printed Material, 1981-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1979-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 4-5)
  - Mathieu, Paul, Archival Resource Key (Box 9)
    - General, 1985-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Photographic Material, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Matthews, Kazuko Kayasuga, Archival Resource Key (Box 9)
    - General, 1985-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Photograph of Matthews, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 9)
      One slide transparency.
  - Matuszewski, Gloria, General, 1994-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Mayeri, Beverly, Archival Resource Key (Box 9)
    - Announcements and Press Releases, DW Gallery, 1990-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Collector Records, 1990-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Consignment Records, 1991-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1988-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Loan Form, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Price Lists, 1990-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Printed Material, 1981-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Re-sale Records, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 19-20)
  - McBride, Kathryn, General, 1984-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - McDonnell, Mark, General, 1983-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Meiners, Dennis, General, 1994-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Melchert, Jim, General, 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Messenger, Mark, General, circa 1992-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Miller, Bradley, General, 1993-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Mills, Rick, General, 1996-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Milnes, Robert, General, 1990-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Miyata, Masako, General, 1990-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Mizuno, Keisuke, General, 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Montgomery, Steven, General, 1996-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Moquin, Richard, General, circa 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Moran, Mike, General, 1995-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Morris, James, Archival Resource Key (Box 9)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Printed Material, 1985-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1985-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 3-4)
  - Morris, William, Archival Resource Key (Box 10)
    - Collector Records, 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Consignment Records, 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1993-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Printed Material, 1983-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Re-sale Records, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1993-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 10-12)
  - Mosman, Timothy, Archival Resource Key (Box 10)
    - General, 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Photographs of Mosman, circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1987-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Musler, Jay, Archival Resource Key (Box 10)
    - Collector Records, 1984-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Consignment Records, 1991-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1984-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Inactive Inventory, 1980-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Invoices, 1981-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Loan Forms, 1994-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Price Lists, 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Printed Material, 1981-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Photographs of Musler, 1982, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 25-26)
  - Myers, Kevin, General, 1996-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Nakata, Rory, General, 1977-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Natzler, Otto and Gertrud, General, 1971-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Nelson, Keiko, General, 1989-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Notkin, Richard, General, circa 1984-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - O'Connor, Casey, General, circa 1996-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Olivier, Diane, Archival Resource Key (Box 10)
    - Correspondence, 1988-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Printed Material, 1985-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1985-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Patti, Thomas, General, 1979-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Pearson, Todd, Archival Resource Key (Box 10)
    - General, 1986-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1986-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Peet, Anne, General, 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Perkins, Flo, General, 1981-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Perotto, Glen Rogers, General, 1986-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Podmore, Amy, Archival Resource Key (Box 11)
    - General, circa 1987-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Includes 2 postcards illustrated by Podmore.
    - Photograph of Podmore, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1987-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 3-4)
  - Popelka, Jeremy, Archival Resource Key (Box 11)
    - General, 1991-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1990-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 6-7)
  - Powers, Pike, General, 1990-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Price, Ken, General, 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Quaglita, Narcissus, General, 1994-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Quinn, Jeanne, General, 1997-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Rainey, Clifford, Archival Resource Key (Box 11)
    - Correspondence, 1992-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Printed Material, 1987-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Photograph of Rainey, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1987-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 15-16)
  - Reinertson, Lisa, Archival Resource Key (Box 11)
    - General, circa 1988-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Photograph of Reinertson, circa 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 18)
      Photograph of the artist working on Martin Luther King, Jr., sculpture.
  - Reiss, Walter, General, 1995-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Reitz, Donald, Archival Resource Key (Box 11)
    - General, 1986-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Photographs of Reitz, circa 1986-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Rhodes, Daniel, General, circa 1964-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Rice, Jacqueline, General, 1984-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Riley, Cheryl Renee, General, circa 1988-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Ritchey, Rik, General, 1990-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Ritchie, Gail, General, 1985-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Ritchie, Leah, General, 1991-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Roberts, Amy, General, 1983-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 28)
    Includes card with an original print.
  - Roberts, Gregory, Archival Resource Key (Box 11)
    - Correspondence, 1991-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 29-30)
    - Printed Material, 1993-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 31-32)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 33-34)
  - Roberts, Nancy Rawls, General, 1992-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Rock, Joellyn, Photographic Material, circa 1989-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Rohlfing, John G., General, 1988-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Rosdol, Leslie, General, 1992-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Rosen, Annabeth, Archival Resource Key (Box 12)
    - General, 1995-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Printed Material, 1995-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1994-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Rosenberg, Edor, General, circa 1987-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Roth, Leslie, Photographic Material, circa 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Rotschild, Jason, Photographic Material, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Ruffner, Ginny, Archival Resource Key (Box 12)
    - General, 1984-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Printed Material, 1985-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Rush, Jerry, General, 1994-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Sabrina, Amy, Correspondence, 1987-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Sakway, Hap, General, 1990-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Saloman, Judith, General, circa 1988-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Samios, William, General, 1992-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Sanders, Terri Ann, General, 1989-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Sasaki, Hitoshi, General, circa 1983-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Savage, Juta, Archival Resource Key (Box 12)
    - General, 1983-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 19)
      Oversized illustrated letter of drawings for Teapot Invitational housed in OV 21.
    - Photographic Material, circa 1980-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 20-21)
  - Scanga, Italo, General, 1992-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Scheer, Elaine, General, 1985-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Scheid, Anne, General, 1994-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Scheiner, Michael, General, 1988-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Schnabel, Jo Ann, General, 1988-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Schwarz, June, General, 1969-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Scotchie, Virginia, Archival Resource Key (Box 12)
    - General, 1983-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1983-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Sedestrom, Robert, General (includes a handmade card), circa 1987-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Shaffer, Mary, Printed Material, 1992-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Shay, Robert, General, 1983-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Sherrill, Michael, General, 1994-1996, Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Shrosbree, James R., General, circa 1980-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Silliman, Christopher, Archival Resource Key (Box 12)
    - General, circa 1990-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1989-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Silver, Anna, General, circa 1984-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Simon, Sandy, General, circa 1982-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Slusky, Joe, General, 1985-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Smith, Barbara Bell, Archival Resource Key (Box 13)
    - Announcements and Press Releases, DW Gallery, 1986-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Printed Material, 1985-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1985-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Sperry, Robert, Archival Resource Key (Box 13)
    - General, 1986-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Printed Material, 1981-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 9-10)
    - Photographs of Sperry, circa 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Stanbridge, Linda, Archival Resource Key (Box 13)
    - General, 1993-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1993-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Statom, Therman, Archival Resource Key (Box 13)
    - Active Inventories, 1992-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Announcements and Press Releases, DW Gallery, 1992-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Biography, [1997]; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Collector Records, 1992-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Consignment Records, 1992-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1984, 1992-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Price Lists, 1992-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Printed Material, 1981-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Photographs of Statom, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1990-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 23-24)
    - Photographic Material and Permissions, circa 1992-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Stein, Livia, General, 1986-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Stephenson, John, General, 1985-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Stewart, William, 1995-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Strasser, Dharma, 1997-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Sugiyami, Michio, 1986-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 30)
    Also Ceramic Art Park, Shiga, Japan.
  - Sullivan, Karen W., General, circa 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Swanson, Richard, General, 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Takayama-Ogawa, Joan, General, circa 1991-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Tarantino, Claudia, General, 1987-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Taylor, Yoshio, Archival Resource Key (Box 13)
    - Announcements and Press Releases, DW Gallery, 1983-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence, 1983-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Printed Material, 1982-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Photographs of Taylor, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1983-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 2-3)
  - Tedesco, Photographic Material, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Temkin, Noam, General, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Terestman, Julie, General, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Thayer, Susan, General, circa 1992-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Theiss, Vernon, General, circa 1988-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Thompson, Cappy, General, circa 1996-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Tomb, David, General, 1989-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 10)